Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: February 9, 2024

Thank you for visiting the PanelBucks website located at www.PanelBucks.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of PanelBucks (“PanelBucks,” “we,” “our” or “us”). This PanelBucks Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers our treaent of personal information and other information that we collect when an end-user visitor to the Site (“subscriber,” “you” or “your”) accesses or uses: (a) the Site; (b) the Site’s viewable text, graphics and other material (collectively, “Content”); (c) a variety of third-party, aggregated pay-for-participation surveys ("Surveys") as made available on or through the Site by PanelBucks;  
**Please note, if you are a resident of, or reside in, the United kingdom or a European Union Member State, you are not permitted to use the Site and/or Site Offers.**

Subscribers with disabilities who wish to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format can contact us by e-mailing us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com); or sending us U.S. mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780

Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings set forth in the PanelBucks Website Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”). **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE UTILIZE THE Site Offers.**

#### **State Specific Privacy Rights**

Residents of the States of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah and Virginia, businesses organized under the laws of the State of California, as well as California-based employees of, and California residents who submit job applicants to, PanelBucks (collectively, “Covered Subscribers”), are afforded additional rights pursuant to applicable state law. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights as a Covered Subscriber.

#### 1\. Your California Privacy Rights

Shine the Light. If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to learn how your “personal information” (as defined in the Shine the Light Law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83) is shared with third-parties, what categories of personal information we have shared with third-parties in the preceding year, as well as the names and addresses of those third-parties, please e-mail us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com); or send us U.S. Mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780

Further, if you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com); or send us U.S. Mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780. Please be advised that where California State residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law.

California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). In addition to the foregoing, if you are a resident of the State of California, certain other privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the CCPA, including the right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights under the CCPA as a California State resident.

The California Privacy Rights Act (“CPRA”). In addition to the foregoing, if you are a resident of the State of California, certain other privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the CPRA, including the right to correct personal information we have collected about you, the right to opt-out of our use/sharing of your sensitive personal information, the right to know how long we retain your sensitive and non-sensitive personal information, the right to know what sensitive personal information about you we have collected, whether your sensitive personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of sensitive personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that sensitive personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights under the CPRA as a California State resident.

Browser “Do Not Track” Signals. Most browsers contain a “do-not-track” setting. In general, when a “do-not-track” setting is active, the subscriber’s browser notifies other websites that the subscriber does not want her/his personal information and online behavior to be tracked and used, for example, for interest-based advertising. As required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (“CalOPPA”), we are required to inform you that, as is the case with most websites, we do not honor or alter our behavior when a Site subscriber has activated the “do-not-track” setting on her/his browser; _provided, however_, that you may have certain rights with respect to the use of automated technologies to deliver targeted advertising to you, as well as to create profiles about you using your personal information.

#### 2\. Your Colorado Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Colorado, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Colorado Privacy Act (“CPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights under the CPA as a Colorado State resident.

#### 3\. Your Connecticut Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Connecticut, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Connecticut Data Privacy Act (“CDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights under the CDPA as a Connecticut State resident.

#### 4\. Your Nevada Privacy Rights

Nevada State residents have the right to submit opt-out requests to website operators instructing those website operators not to sell any “covered information” that the website operators have collected about Nevada State residents to any third party data broker(s). Covered information includes a consumer’s name, postal and email address, telephone number and Social Security Number, and includes the Information described below in the “Personal Information Collected” section.

If you are a Nevada State resident and you wish to exercise your right to request that we to stop the sale of your Information to third party data brokers, please e-mail us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com); or send us U.S. Mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780. In your request, please specify that you want to exercise your rights to opt-out from the sale of covered information under the Nevada Privacy Law and specify the website that you visited and the email address you registered with. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response.

#### 5\. Your Virginia Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Virginia, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (“VCDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights under the VCDPA as a Virginia State resident.

#### 6\. Your Utah Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Utah, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Utah Consumer Privacy Act (“UCPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers” below for a more complete description of your rights under the UCPA as a Utah State resident.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” shall mean individually identifiable information from or about an individual. We collect personal information when you access the Site Offers and complete the required information request form and/or otherwise provide such information to us. Where a subscriber attempts to utilize the Site Offers, that subscriber may be required to submit, and PanelBucks may collect, some or all of the following information: (a) full name; (b) full mailing address; (c) telephone number; (d) e-mail address; (e) date of birth; (f) gender; and (g) any other information requested on the Form. In addition, where a subscriber enters a Contest and, where applicable, is selected as a potential prize winner in connection therewith, PanelBucks may collect some or all of the following: (I) Social Security Number (for prize winners); (II) picture proof of identification, which may include a driver’s license, passport, voting card or similar government issued identification (for prize winners); and (III) any other information requested in connection with the applicable Contest.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, items (I) and (II) in the preceding paragraph shall be referred to as “Sensitive Information.”

##### Use and Sharing of Personal Information

By submitting your personal information by and through the Site Offers, you agree that, subject Applicable State Laws (as defined below): (a) we may share, sell, rent, lease or otherwise provide that personal information (other than Sensitive Information) to any third-party for any purpose permitted by law; (b) **the third parties that we share, sell, rent, lease or otherwise provide your personal information (other than Sensitive Information) may also re-sell your personal information to additional third parties**; and (c) we may work with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our subscribers. These businesses and third-parties may include, but are not limited to: (I) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (II) e-mail marketers; (III) telemarketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (IV) direct marketers. We may also use your personal information to send you promotional messages regarding various PanelBucks products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services that we think may be of interest to you.

Where you submit personal information, we use the personal information that you make available to personalize your experience with the Site and to facilitate the delivery of the applicable Site Offers to you, including to respond to any inquiries made by you.

Your email will only be shared with our preferred mailing partner for the purpose of sending third party promotional email communications.

You also agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Site Offers, and to keep you informed of our other products and services.

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from subscriber lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our subscribers’ personal information as needed to perform these functions for us, but we do not permit them to use subscriber personal information for other purposes.

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience with the Site Offers and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with your use of the Site Offers. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our service Surveys including, without limitation, the Site Offers. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources.

By submitting your personal information by and through the Site Offers, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule and applicable state do-not-call regulations.

Where you provide “prior express consent” within the meaning of the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (47 USC § 227), and its implementing regulations adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (47 CFR § 64.1200), as amended from time-to-time (“TCPA”), you consent to receive telephone calls from PanelBucks, including artificial voice calls, pre-recorded messages and/or calls (including SMS text messages) delivered via automated technology, to the telephone number(s) that you provided. **Please note that you are not required to provide this consent in order to obtain access to the PanelBucks Surveys, and your consent simply allows PanelBucks to contact you via these means. Please be advised that by agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are obligated to immediately inform us if and when the telephone number that you have previously provided to us changes. Without limiting the foregoing, if you: (A) have your telephone number reassigned to another person or entity; (B) give up your telephone number so that it is no longer used by you; (C) port your telephone number to a landline or vice versa; or (D) otherwise stop using that telephone number for any reason (collectively “Phone Number Change”), you agree that you shall promptly notify PanelBucks of the Phone Number Change via e-mail at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com), or by using one of the methods set forth in the “Contact Us” section below**.

We reserve the right to release current or past personal information: (I) in the event that we believe that the Site Offers are being or have been used in violation of the Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; (II) if the information is subpoenaed or requested pursuant to any court order or legal proceeding; _provided, however_, that, where permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena/court order, prior to disclosure of any personal information pursuant to a subpoena; (III) if we are sold, merge with a third-party, or are acquired by a third-party (collectively, “M&A Transactions”) (including where we share your personal information, including Sensitive Information, in connection with the due diligence process associated with a potential M&A Transaction); or (IV) if we are the subject of bankruptcy proceedings. _provided, however_, that if PanelBucks is involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, and/or M&A Transaction, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your personal information.

We reserve the right to release current or past personal information: (A) in the event that we believe that the Site Offers are being or have been used in violation of the Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; (B) if the information is subpoenaed or requested pursuant to any court order or legal proceeding; _provided, however_, that, where permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena/court order, prior to disclosure of any personal information pursuant to a subpoena; or (C) if we are sold, merge with a third-party, are acquired or are the subject of bankruptcy proceedings; _provided, however_, that if PanelBucks is involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your personal information.

You hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with applicable law, including the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time-to-time. Subscribers should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or transferred to third-parties without permission.

##### Non-Personal Information Collection and Use

IP Addresses/Browser Type

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you and your desktop computer and/or mobile device when you visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AT&T). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site Offers and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze usage of the Site Offers.

Cookies

When a subscriber visits the Site, we send one (1) or more cookies and/or gif files (collectively, “Cookies”) to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable subscriber’s computer. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. To find out more about Cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. We use Cookies to improve the quality of the Site Offers, including for storing subscriber preferences and tracking Site-subscriber trends (such as pages opened and length of stay at the Site).

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a subscriber rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Site Offers; _provided, however_, that certain functions of the Site Offers may be impaired or rendered inoperable if the use of Cookies is disabled. We reserve the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

Notwithstanding any other provision, we partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising to you or your business Our partners may place or recognize a cookie on your computer, device, or directly in our emails/communications, and we may share personal information with them if you have submitted such information to us, such as your name, postal address, email address, or device ID. Our partners may link the hashed or obfuscated personal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. Your data may be transferred outside of the country from which it was originally collected.

##### Behavioral Tracking

PanelBucks, as well as third party entities such as Google®, Bing® and Facebook®, use Cookies, pixels and other tracking technology (collectively, “Tracking Technology”) in connection with the Site for purposes of tracking subscribers’ activities (such as websites visited, advertisements selected and pages viewed) after they leave the Site. PanelBucks, and its third-party partners, use this Tracking Technology to target applicable subscribers with advertisements featuring PanelBucks products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services, that may be of interest to applicable subscribers.

Without limiting the foregoing, PanelBucks utilizes the third party services of Everflow Technologies Inc., Everflow® (“Everflow”) and Ifficient Inc. (including its Twyne.io service) to record Site visits from subscribers, track the Site activity of such subscribers, and track the origin of the subscriber among other things, that subscriber "prior express consent" has been provided as required by the TCPA.

In general, subscribers may be able to disable some, but not all, of this tracking activity by utilizing the “Do Not Track” setting or similar options within most major Internet browsers. In addition, subscribers may be able to opt-out of this form of tracking utilizing the options made available by the Network Advertising Initiative or Digital Advertising Alliance.

Further, subscribers can opt-out of certain Google®-related tracking technology, and customize the Google® Display Network ads that they receive, by visiting the Google® Ads Settings at: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) Google® also recommends installing the Google® Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your web browser, which is available here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). To the greatest extent permissible under applicable law, we are not responsible for the tracking practices of third-parties in connection with the Site.

##### Cross Device Tracking

PanelBucks may track subscribers’ use of the PanelBucks Surveys across various devices, including subscribers’ personal computers and mobile devices, in order to optimize and personalize use of the Site Offers. PanelBucks may collect certain subscriber personal information across various devices.

##### Aggregate Data

PanelBucks reserves the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about subscribers of the PanelBucks Surveys for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and other characteristics of PanelBucks Surveys subscribers as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information.

##### Third-Party Websites

This Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites including, without limitation, the websites owned and operated by Merchants, Third-Party Providers and/or Social Media Websites. PanelBucks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of these third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and PanelBucks has no responsibility or liability relating to them.

##### Security of Your Personal Information

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our subscribers’ personal information. When subscribers make personal information available to us, their personal information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any personal information offline). Where our registration/application process prompts subscribers to enter sensitive information (such as financial information), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, that information is encrypted with industry standard encryption technology.

In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

##### Children’s Privacy

Visitors under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at the Site. PanelBucks does not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under eighteen (18) years of age. PanelBucks encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

##### Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

* To opt-out of receiving e-mail and other forms of communication from us, you can: (a) follow the instructions included in the applicable e-mail message or other communication; or (b) e-mail us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com);
* To opt-out from telemarketing calls, please follow the prompts on the call or contact customer service;
* To opt-out from SMS/text messaging, reply STOP to the text/SMS message received;
* To opt-out of browser-based push notifications, please disable the notifications at the time you receive the notification or disable notifications through your browser’s settings; and
* To-opt out of cookies, interest-based advertising and/or third-party analytics, please see the section above.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your request for Site Offers, your participation in the Surveys, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. To opt-out of receiving Site Offers\-related and/or inquiry response-related messages from PanelBucks, you must cease requesting and/or utilizing the Site Offers, cease participating in the Surveys and/or cease submitting inquiries to PanelBucks, as applicable.

##### Deleting, Modifying and Updating Your Information

At your request, we will: (a) inform you of what personal information we have on file for you; (b) amend the personal information that we have on file for you; and/or (c) remove personal information that you have provided to us, or that we have collected. You may do so by e-mailing us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com). We ask individual subscribers to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Please be advised that deleting your personal information may terminate your access to certain of the Site Offers. If you wish to continue using the full complement of Site Offers, you may not be able to delete all of the personal information that we have on file for you.

Please be further advised that, after you delete your personal information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

##### Transfer of Personal Information Internationally

If you are visiting the Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting the Site and/or otherwise communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers. Even if your jurisdiction does not have the same privacy laws as the jurisdiction where our servers are located, we will treat your information as subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

PanelBucks reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Site that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personal information changes, PanelBucks will notify subscribers by: (a) sending the modified policy to our subscribers via email; and/or (b) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner and we will only use your information in this different manner where you opt-in to such use.

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices in general, please e-mail us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com) or send us U.S. Mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780.

#### **Privacy Provisions for Covered Subscribers**

These Provisions for Covered Subscribers (“Provisions”) supplement, and do not limit in any way, the Privacy Policy set forth above. These Privacy Provisions apply solely to the Covered Subscribers, who are residents of the States of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia and Utah, as well as businesses organized under the laws of the State of California. We adopt these Provisions in compliance with the CCPA, CPRA, CPA, CDPA, VCDPA and UCPA (collectively, “Applicable State Laws”). Any terms defined in Applicable State Laws have the same meaning when used in these Privacy Provisions. Subscribers with disabilities who wish to access these Privacy Provisions in an alternative format can contact us by emailing us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com); or sending us U.S. Mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780

Categories of Information We Collect

We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular Covered Subscriber or device (“personal information”). In particular, we have collected the following categories of personal information from Covered Subscribers within the last twelve (12) months:

| **Category** | **Examples** | **Collected** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| A. Identifiers. | A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, telephone number, or other similar identifiers. | YES |
| B. Personal information categories listed inApplicable State Laws. | A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, postal address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or State identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. | NO  |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under Applicable State Laws or federal law. | Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information). | YES |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity. | Browsing history, search history, information on a CA Subscriber's interaction with a website, application or advertisement. | YES |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information. | Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | YES |
| L. Sensitive Personal Information. | A Social Security number, driver’s license number, state identification card number, or passport number. Account log-in information, financial account, or debit or credit card number used in combination with any required security code, access code, password, or log-in credentials necessary to access an account. Precise geolocation, racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, or union membership. The contents of a consumer’s U.S. mail, electronic mail, or text messages unless the business is the intended recipient, and a consumer’s genetic data. | NO  |

Personal information does not include:

* Publicly available information from government records.
* De-identified or aggregated Covered Subscriber information.
* Information excluded from the scope of Applicable State Laws, such as:
    * health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data; and
    * personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Drier's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.

We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources (with the specific categories of personal information indicated in parenthesis):

* Directly from our Covered Subscribers. For example, from online registration forms that our Covered Subscribers submit to us in connection with our membership services, our coupons-related products and/or services, our sweepstakes and promotions, and the other products and/or services that we offer by and through the Site. (Category A, B, C, K and L)
* Indirectly from our Covered Subscribers. For example, through information we collect from our Covered Subscribers in the course of providing our products and/or services to them. (Category A, B, C, K and L)
* Directly and indirectly from activity on the Site. This includes the type of browser that you use (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of your Internet Service Provider. In addition, we obtain certain Site usage details and analytics as same are collected automatically by us and our third party partners. (Category F)
* When our Covered Subscribers interact with us on our social media accounts, including commenting on and/or liking our posts. (Category A, B, C and F)
* From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the products and/or services that we offer to our Covered Subscribers. For example, third party entities that assist us in sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from Covered Subscriber lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. (Category A, B, C, k and L)

Retention of Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information

We retain all categories of your personal information and Sensitive Information (including the information set forth in the “Personal Information Collected” section above) that we collect for the maximum period permitted by applicable law. We may also use certain criteria to determine whether and when to delete certain categories of collected personal and sensitive personal information including:

* Date of collection.
* Frequency of consumer interaction with us.
* Last interaction the consumer had with us.
* Whether the purpose of collection has been completed.

Use of Personal Information

We may use or disclose the personal information that we collect for one or more of the following business purposes (with the specific categories of personal information indicated in parenthesis):

* To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you provide us with personal information in connection with your registration for our Surveys, sweepstakes and promotions, and/or our other products and/or services, we will use that information to process your registration. (Category A, B, C, K and L)
* To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* To create, maintain, customize and secure your account with us. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* To provide you with e-mail, direct mail and telemarketing messages concerning certain PanelBucks products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services, that we believe may be of interest to you. (Category A, B, C, F and K)
* To deliver relevant Site content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you. (Category A, B, C, F and K)
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including the Site’s Terms and Conditions. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* To improve the Site and better present its contents to you. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* For customer service purposes and to respond to inquiries from you. (Category A and B)
* For testing, research, analysis and product development. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* As necessary or appropriate to protect our rights, property or safety, and that of our clients or others. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the Applicable State Law. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)
* To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred. (Category A, B, C, F, K and L)

We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated or incompatible purposes without providing you with notice.

Sharing Personal Information

Subject to your right to opt-out of such sharing/sale, we may share, rent and/or sell your personal information: (a) with/to third parties for marketing purposes (but not Sensitive Information); and (b) for each of the other business purposes set forth above. The third parties that we share/sell your personal information with/to may also re-sell your personal information to additional third parties.

When we disclose personal information to a third party service provider or other entity, we enter into a contractual relationship that describes the purpose for which such third party may use the personal information and requires that third party to both keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose other than the performance of its services under the applicable contract. Please note, we do not collect information from CA Subscribers that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age and we do not share or sell the personal information of Covered Subscribers that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age. Without limiting the foregoing, we have not shared or sold the personal information of Covered Subscribers that we actually know are less than sixteen (16) years of age.

Non-Discrimination

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights under Applicable State Laws. Unless permitted by Applicable State Laws, we will not:

* Deny you goods or services;
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties;
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; and/or
* Retaliate against any employee, job applicant or independent contractor and/or
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments about these Provisions, our Privacy Policy, the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under Applicable State Laws, please do not hesitate to contact us by either:

* Emailing us at: [support@PanelBucks.com](mailto:support@panelbucks.com); or
* Sending us U.S. mail to: PanelBucks, 360 E. 1st Street, #4226, Tustin, CA 92780

© Copyright 2024 PanelBucks All Rights Reserved
